<resources>
    <string name="app_name">约吧</string>
    <string name="news_title1">杭州太子湾郁金香含苞待放 </string>
    <string name="news_title2">三月，你也可以是“神秘巨星”</string>
    <string name="news_title3">服务外包比赛火热报名中</string>
    <string name="news_title4">我校图书馆六楼“芸香咖啡”开业</string>
    <string name="news_title5">阳光长跑开始啦啊哈哈哈哈</string>
    <string name="news_title6">开心麻花爆笑舞台剧《李茶的姑妈》</string>
    <string name="news_title7">海皇星2018 第四届双浦樱花节</string>
    <string name="news_title8">直到世界尽头—8090经典动漫演唱会</string>
    <string name="news_title9">智慧城市研究中心应邀参加第七届宁波智博会</string>
    <string name="news_title10">杭州图书馆常规志愿活动开始招志愿者了</string>
    <string name="news_title11">2018届华为网络技术大赛</string>
    <string name="news_title12">云鼎大讲堂第二讲“区块链在未来AI教育中的价值应用”开讲</string>
    <string name="news_content1">3月6日，杭州太子湾公园的第一批郁金香已含苞待放，与前期开放的山樱、水仙、虞美人等花品相映生辉，太子湾公园将迎来早春最美的花季。</string>
    <string name="news_content2"> 今年，青叔将一如既往地为大家提供“衣”往情深、我是一个喷洗匠、净镜活动、饮水思源等便民服务，做你的贴心小帮手，让这个春天更加温暖美好。</string>
    <string name="news_content3">"中国大学生服务外包创新创业大赛"（以下简称大赛），是响应国家关于鼓励服务外包产业发展、加强服务外包人才培养的相关战略举措与号召，举办的每年一届的全国性竞赛。主要目的是搭建产学结合的大学生服务外包创新创业能力展示平台。参赛队伍本科生为主，自由组队。大赛开放方式竞赛，经过报名参赛、自主选题、分散备赛和集中答辩的环节，评选出相应的优秀团队。</string>
    <string name="news_content4">9月19日，由文一公司和校图书馆联合筹建的图书馆六楼咖啡吧——芸香咖啡正式开业。当天，副校长吕金海、徐江荣及工会、学工处、图书馆、文一公司等相关部门领导亲临现场指导工作，，希望文一公司进一步转变观念，提升主动服务意识，采取切实有效的措施，大力打造舒适、文明、安全的学习、生活、就餐环境。</string>
    <string name="news_content5">本学期的阳光长跑活动你准备好了吗，不管你准没准备好，反正该跑的总要跑的。一如既往，本学期也有“每周之星”和“千里马”奖励哦，会对每周男女前五名颁发奖状和奖品。尽管长跑对速度上的要求不高，但还是需要同学们做好热身，并在奔跑结束后做好放松与拉伸。要约跑的童鞋可以约起来了</string>
    <string name="news_content6">3月16,17日，杭州大剧院(歌剧院),将中国喜剧灵魂注入百老汇经典《查理的姑妈》！本来只想"捞点好处"的沧海，却猛地陷入一场觊觎财富的谄媚游戏中。两个中年男人为"傍姑妈"疯狂求爱，事情越来越失去控制，然而这一切全在真姑妈的监视之中……</string>
    <string name="news_content7">3月10日-4月10日，海皇星生态探险乐园拥有近20万方浪漫樱花，有1999米的樱花大道、4000多株樱花树，园区几乎囊括了所以的樱花品种。谈谈情，说说爱，方不辜负明媚春光。预计最佳赏花时间/中国红樱花：3月5日-3月10日，白色樱花：3月19日-3月27日</string>
    <string name="news_content8">4月30日。可能是2018年最能唤回你青春记忆的演唱会,可能是2018年最让你感受勇气与爱的演唱会。早已陷入生活的少年们，这是一份为青春复苏准备的礼物，两个小时不间断的热唱，首首你都耳熟能详，曲曲你都能一起合唱，带你回到充满热血沸腾、肆意做梦、天真烂漫的少年时代。年少的激情，虽然尘封，但却一触即燃</string>
    <string name="news_content9">9月8日至10日，第七届中国智慧城市技术与应用产品博览会在宁波举行。本届智博会围绕“智能牵动未来，智慧引领时代”主题，通过展览展示、主题论坛产业对接、新品发布会、项目签约等重要活动，展示探索新型智慧城市建设与智能经济融合发展的城市经济发展道路。我校智慧城市研究中心受邀参展，集中展示了中心近年来在顶层设计、智慧水务、智慧健康和物联网等领域的新技术、新产品、新应用。</string>
    <string name="news_content10">位于上城区的杭州图书馆环境雅致、静谧，书香飘逸，学习氛围浓厚。志愿工作只要整理一下图书或者使用一下检索电脑就好。工作之余可以自由阅览书籍报刊，力荐。</string>
    <string name="news_content11">2018年，又一年，华为网技我们又来了，为了方便让同学们进行技术交流，我们将邀请已获得华为offer的沈佳舜学长，还有其他进入决赛的学长做比赛经验分享。IT狂人仍会秉承服务杭电原则为大家答疑并提供免费的网络技术培训。第三届华为网技，期待未知，加油HDUer</string>
    <string name="news_content12">1月25日，云鼎大讲堂第二讲在我校下沙校区科技馆322会议室开讲，由加拿大爱酷公司CEO韩强博士作“区块链在未来AI教育中的价值应用”报告。计算机学院副院长孔万增教授主持报告会，计算机学院、会计学院的师生代表及相关企业人士参加讲座。云鼎大讲堂是中国财务云服务研究院创建的品牌活动，将不定期邀请国内外财务云、云计算、大数据、人工智能等领域的知名专家学者作学术报告。本次讲座内容丰富，深入浅出，令与会者深受启发。</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login_test">Sign in</string>

    <!-- Strings related to login -->
    <string name="prompt_email">Email</string>
    <string name="prompt_password">Password (optional)</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in">Sign in or register</string>
    <string name="action_sign_in_short">Sign in</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_email">This email address is invalid</string>
    <string name="error_invalid_password">This password is too short</string>
    <string name="error_incorrect_password">This password is incorrect</string>
    <string name="error_field_required">This field is required</string>
    <string name="permission_rationale">"Contacts permissions are needed for providing email
        completions."
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_appointment_history">AppointmentHistoryActivity</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
</resources>
